HANNAH LEONG

TECHNOLOGY DEGREE APPRENTICE

hannah.leo64@gmail.com

07948381115

www.linkedin.com/in/hannah-leo

PROFILE

I am currently a final year technology degree apprentice with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC), studying computer science at the University of Birmingham. I specialise in software engineering but also have an interest in cyber security, image processing and robotics.

EDUCATION

BSc Computer Science with Digital Technology Partnership, University of Birmingham (2018-2022)

Degree apprenticeship with year in industry sponsored by PwC

Nonsuch High School for Girls (2011-2018)

A-levels: A*, A, A, B in Mathematics, Further Mathematics, Computer Science and Physics with A* in EPQ GCSEs: 1 A**, 7 A*, 3 A, 1 B

EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present

Technology Degree Apprentice • PwC

2018: Summer placement spent designing and building a chatbot, implementing Google Cloud Platform capabilities in an Agile method. 2020-2021: Year placement working on projects ranging from a global mobility tool to a personalised online learning platform. Gained experience with Microsoft Azure services, bug testing and fixing, and multiple programming languages (e.g. C#, JavaScript, SQL, YAML, Python)

2017-2018

Tutor • First Class Learning

Leading group tuition sessions for children up to GCSE age

2014-2018

Restaurant worker • Gold Medal House Delivering takeaway meals

KEY SKILLS -

Problem solving

Organisation

Teamwork

Leadership

Critical thinking

"Keen to learn" - Inquisitive

"Determined"

"Analytical"

"Hard working"

"Enthusiastic"

VOLUNTEERING

2017-2018

School mentor • Nonsuch High School

Supporting younger pupils with their studies and sitting in as a teaching aid in computer science classes

2016-2017

Donation Organiser • St Raphael's Hospice Charity ShopSorting through and organising charity shop donations

2014-2017

Craft Leader • Children's Holiday Club

Helping organise and plan crafts for a children's annual holiday club

2015-2016

Animal Care • Bobtails Rabbit and Guinea Pig Rescue

Animal care at a local rescue centre